What's your favorite place?
>> I don't have a favorite place. I have my
favorite sequel.
>> It's almost time for us to land.
I love when [music]
I
[music]
Time to receive the name.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah. [music] Oh
yeah.
[music]
>> I owe you when I come back here.
>> No. Greetings to IG.
>> Sure. Sure.
>> That our small baby.
>> By the time I'll come back, it'll be
two.
>> Exactly. [laughter]
I'm holding [music]
[music]
[music] this. The overr.
The over. [music]
Hey guys, I am here for my laser
appointment.
>> You know this laser right now. This is
skin analytics.
>> Cute, cute, cute, cute, cute.
admit it ain't a fair fight,
[music]
>> guys. I done my forehead. I just made my
hair yesterday and I have to rock it.
But yes, this is the first time ever I
am meeting up with my appointment like
even way before the time. So, I'm
supposed to do my lashes but I didn't
book early enough and there was no
available slots. lucky for me because
they are my people. They made sure that
they find a way to put me in cuz usually
they start by 9:00, but they said I
should come by 7:00 and I literally go
here by 6:57 a.m. because I cannot
afford to miss it. Like at this point,
they are the only people I trust with my
eye, my lashes, everything, my brow. I
don't want to go anywhere. I'm so happy
I was finally able to get a spot here
now. Seems like they're not open yet.
>> Should I come in?
>> Yes, ma'am. Morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Thank you so much. You're
welcome. [laughter]
I'm fine. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you guys so much. These are my people.
[laughter]
Thank you so so much.
Guys, I'm done with my lashes and I also
curved my brows. See, if you're in Lagos
and you're looking for where to do your
brows, like brow ammunition, your
lashes, or even micro, is it micro
blading? Yeah, you should definitely
come here. Please come to beish. Do you
like it? You're so pretty.
>> Thank you.
Come to beauty Nigeria. Come like their
service is topnotch. This is why I would
never ever try somebody else. Please
just come to be Nigeria. Come and try
them.
>> [music]
>> Guys, we are on our way to somewhere. Oh
my god. I don't know if I should talk
about this now, but I'm sure that by the
time this video will be up, it should be
out there. But yeah, um Booby is opening
a store in Lagos. Ah, quack quack quack
quack. Congratulations to her. So, we
are currently on our way to her store. I
want to see it cuz I won't be around for
the shop opening. But at least let's get
to see the store, congratulate her, and
pray for her as well. The road is a bit
bumpy. So, I'm close by. I want to
quickly do that because I have other
appointments. It's a day before my trip.
So, you know, you guys, it's not news
that I always plan everything last
minute. I literally put every single
thing the day before my trip. So I will
have to do this quickly then go for my
facial
[music]
boo.
Good morning.
be small as income. [laughter]
Thank you. How are you? Good morning.
Hey, congratulations.
55 Jesus. Well done. Cat on. Jesus.
[snorts]
Catws and cartoons of things. Don't say
you don't fix any film job because I
know you.
>> I know you guys. This girl like she
loves money too much. [laughter]
Am I lying?
Yeah, I'm lying.
>> I've cancelled all my
>> You better You better because you need
to make out time to do this one. Hey,
make our market. So, boo boo
your babies. Look at cars. Please. Oh,
these things cannot here for they have
to go. They have to go. If you buy, we
restock.
>> We have the big ones.
The bigger ones. small room.
>> E. Hey God, this is so fine. Boo. See,
boo boo. Now she's established. She's
establishing more and more because from
here we will get to a bigger space. See
you. It's actually very fine. I love it.
Notebooks. Find fine ones actually.
>> Stories.
>> Oh, you have story books as well. Yes.
>> See,
keep copying them. They learn keywords.
Please. We have so many things. T-shirt.
Uh, water bottles. Yeah, cute water
bottles and cute beautiful dresses.
Don't worry, you'll get to see more of
it by the time everything is arranged.
When the shop is finally open, you'll
get the location. Come shop for your
babies because babies too. Your kids,
your kids, they need to look good. So,
I'm so proud of you.
So, so well, congratulations once again,
little boy.
Open bigger and how it goes for you. You
will not have any reason to regret this
decision
to take you higher and higher.
>> Thank you so much for coming.
>> You're welcome. You're welcome. You're
welcome.
>> Let's go
to Sarah. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> Okay.
And I'm busy.
>> Bye. Bye.
When I when I call
I am here to do my facials.
>> Hello.
>> Hi.
>> Good morning.
Thank you. I'm fine. When you see when
your sister is the CEO, you get to chill
in her office even when she's not
around.
See me flexing.
Can I get
>> people to give you chinch? Hey, no.
So you you give someone that is not your
customer chi.
I want you to [laughter]
turn off the AC.
>> Okay. What's my job?
>> Yes, I have a cold.
>> All right.
>> I'm the new CEO
[laughter] of Skin Analytics.
I've taken over. So, you can come to me
for anything skin procedure. If your
before is better than your after. Sorry.
[laughter]
>> I think your after is better than
before.
>> No, because you're going to come to me
too.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You're tired.
>> No, I have fever.
>> Fever.
Hey, sorry. Hug me now. Room. Hey, you
guys. See my room. I don't know is not
feeling like. Can you go out? Sorry.
>> Hey, you don't look
you know I turn off this AC there's one
kind of sickness in the air
>> and I'm scared of falling sick
>> in Abuja. I said I use speed cuz I'm
feeling it already. How did you do your
lash this morning?
>> Ah, you can't do facial.
>> Why this still? Even I should protect
it. Still make it fall off.
>> You guys, I wasn't I wasn't able to do
my facials anymore. I did my lashes and
most times you have to steam your face
and all of that. So, it's not
reasonable. If not, my lashes will fall
off. But luckily, my skin is
flourishing. It's not so bad. We just
skipped that part. Right now, I'm at the
mall. I want to get some skin care
essential for my trip.
[music]
[music and singing]
Come meet me at the
so high.
No one can make us [music] slow down.
Don't want to lose it. What we got?
Don't want to lose it. No, I don't. No,
[music] I don't. There's no confusing.
[singing]
This is love.
Baby, keep moving. [singing]
Don't stop. [music] Don't stop.
We got it.
You guys, I went to buy one of my just
one of my skin care products. I'm even
ashamed. I can't even see how much I got
it. But at this point, I say what I said
at this point, Clarence needs to put me
on their PR list. I beg you because God
just one just one product is not funny.
Please, if you know how I can get on the
appear list, [music]
[music]
>> you guys, it is currently past 10 and I
promise you, I haven't even started
packing. I just did my nails. Let me
show you. I just did my nails and look
at my things.
I don't know when I'll ever get used to
packing like a normal person like get my
things ready like every normal person
and it will make me now I probably won't
sleep at night. I wanted to watch
football cuz I was downstairs initially
watching football but I just remember
that I haven't packed and I had to rush
upstairs. So let me see what I can do
the next 2 to 3 hours.
[music] You guys, I am on my way to the
airport. I'm running I'm not actually
running late if I'm going to be very
honest. I'm not running that late. I
should get there early enough actually.
But I made content this morning.
[laughter]
life of a content creator, an
influencer,
an actor, a YouTuber. Ah, so I made
content and he delayed me a little. I
look really good. I look so pretty. You
guys are going to see the content. By
the time this video up, you obviously
would have seen it on my Instagram or my
Tik Tok or my YouTube shots, anywhere,
everywhere.
[singing]
In Jesus name we have worship.
>> Amen.
>> All our hearts in the mighty name
[music]
for
you something.
Thank you.
>> Hey guys,
I finally finished with everything. I am
done with my check in. So, I have
checked in. Everything went smoothly.
They tried to frustrate me this morning.
My girl wanted to follow me inside the
airport and there was this lady that was
just very rude for no reason. She was so
rude. She refused and like I was
pleading. I was like, "Please, I need
her help." And I wanted her to follow me
so she could take pictures for me as
well. But this lady just blatantly said
no. But at some point she was like, "You
want her to follow you, right?" And when
she said that, I just knew that she was
saying it because obviously she wanted
me to pay. At the usual way, I'm very
good at tipping people. I would I could
tip her, but the way she acted, I just
knew that she did not deserve money. So
at that point, I just told you, you
know, was just go, just go. I'll handle
everything myself. And luckily the guy
that assisted me with my luggage, he was
really friendly. So he helped me all
through. I was so pissed. But I mean I
met good people. I met really good
people. It would have been so helpful.
My check in process was so smooth and
they've actually announced the
pre-boarding announcement. But I am
here. I look so good. By the way, I need
to see if I can show you guys my full
feet.
Hey guys, I wanted to take pictures and
I was so shy but virtually I met this
very sweet lady. Hi, good morning
very sweet lady and hi. Thank you. I met
this sweet lady and I just walked up to
her. I was like, "Please, can you take a
picture of me?" And she was nice enough
to agree. Oh my god, I'm so cold. I'm
very cold. I'm actually shy to recording
because I mean it's Nigeria. People
would always say when you carry your
camera and you're recording, we're doing
it anyways. Hi.
You're literally wondering what I am
doing with this camera.
>> Hi.
>> Good morning.
>> Yeah.
Thank you.
[music]
>> [music]
>> We made it. We bought it already and
we'll be taking off soon.
I literally have to get used to this
step. Why do I feel very shy?
>> [music]
>> What would you like for lunch?
>> Uh, the brace beef shot rib. Yes.
All right.
>> Thank you so much. If you need anything,
my name is Julene. Nice to meet you.
You're welcome. Heat.
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat. N.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat up here. [music]
It's almost time for us to land. I
didn't really get to sleep enough today
for some reason. I don't know why, but
I'm just happy that we're about to land
now. Hope the immigration process will
go very smoothly. That's my prayer. By
the way, I have a mask because I have a
cold. That's why I have to wear a face
mask all the time I'm flying. I always
catch cold easily.
>> [music]
>> So I am at the lounge.
They moved my flight.
Got something to eat.
I'm hungry. I have no choice.
>> It's not very bad.
I just made the worst hot chocolate
ever. I'm so tired. I'm tired. I'm
hungry.
>> I'm still standing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
[music]
Fear be won't catch me. When I heard
that sound, I was like, "Emergency
where?" Emergency what?
Guys, I just go here. Please, I just go
here.
It's happening again. There you go. I
wonder what the emergency is. I just go
here.
when I pity us. I'm headed to my
boarding gate. I hope by the time I get
there, they've not sting cuz I don't
want to stand on the queue for too long.
Finally, when I got to the boarding
gate, they had steboarding already. So,
I just rushed literally run. I feel like
I'm going to sleep all through this cuz
my eyes are so heavy. I'm so tired. They
said the weather wasn't good, so they
had to delay flights, cancel some and
all of that.
Hey guys, we're in North Carolina.
Welcome to Raleigh. I'm still very much
cold, so I'm not taking off my face
mask.
Hi, bro.
>> Good. Good morning, sir.
>> Good morning.
>> Hey. Hey. Cannot come with me.
>> I know. I know.
>> Oh my god. It was scary. It was scary.
It was so shaky
>> and we've been having a lot of um rain
this area because the weather has been
so when I say it's hot
>> like you think that we do well
>> just this one that was I'm not even
going to lie I was a bit panicky but
then [music]
[music]
guys
I'm home now it's past 2 almost 3.
I had to quickly take off my wig because
my head feels like it's about to fall
off my body. I'm so tired. Everyone is
sleeping. Like I just wanted to make
this video quickly because I said I was
going to stay true to this vlog. If not,
I would have stopped.
But I am tired. Look at my eyes. Like I
literally haven't slept properly. I'm
home. I'm so grateful to God for joining
me. Hey there.
Hi.
Guys, I'm about to meet my nephew for
first time.
Ch.
I have to go wash my hand.
>> How are you?
>> I'm fine. It was I's birthday today as
well. Happy birthday to you. you.
Happy birthday. Thank you so much.
>> Are you excited?
>> Yes.
>> Hi.
>> We
mama. Who's that?
Mama.
>> A dizzy.
>> Who is this?
>> A dog.
>> Hey, I thought forgotten you. Who is
this? Mama.
>> Yes.
>> Jesus Christ. [clears throat]
>> Mama is Chi. Mama, come say hi to
Chi-Chi.
>> Mama, come. Let me say hi to you now.
Come. It's Chi.
Hi, baby girl. You've grown so much.
It's Chi
Chi. Chi Chi.
>> What is this?
What is this? Mama,
>> who is this?
>> She wants to come down. She can't
remember me. Hey,
how she remember you talk about?
>> Hi guys. Who is this?
>> She's just distracted.
Who is this? Oh my chi.
She's distracted. Don't worry, guys. You
don't see see my baby girl don't
remember Chi. She don't remember Chi-Chi
again. Eh, she don't remember Chi.
Say hi, guys. Say hi, guys. Say hi,
Chi-Chi.
She's shy, you guys. It's the morning
after I did it. I came to surprise. She
She has refused to act correct to me.
It's all good. It's [snorts] all good.
>> You look like
>> It's all good.
I couldn't even shower. I'm not even
going to lie to you. See, I'm still
wearing the same clothes. It was almost
as if my head was falling off my body.
And if I didn't go to bed, I was going
to faint. So, pardon me, child. I'm
pink.
Don't be pain.
>> I'm very pained.
You want to play with me but you not
mention chih [screaming]
hey see Ronaldo I become Ronaldo
because I never greet my mama she the
hide
I must say a baby
[laughter]
I Sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep,
sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep. [laughter]
>> So guys, this is I don't even know what
day. Let me try to clip this so it
doesn't make a noise here. But yeah,
guys, I don't know what day it is, but
this is yes, day two of my um stay in
the US. I came in yesterday. I didn't
vlog after I um met Adisia and
everything. I was too tired. Honestly, I
was jetlagged. I was tired. I wanted to
just spend time with the family. And at
that point, I just knew I had to keep my
camera. But this is day two. Like I
said, they all just stepped out. I mean,
mama, I husband Ada and the newborn. So,
yeah. If by the time I upload this
video, that means it's already out there
that IG has put to birth our baby boy,
our very cute, handsome, healthy baby
boy. And that's going to be the delay
why this video won't come out
immediately because obviously I want her
to make that announcement first before I
post my video cuz I know some people are
very I know you guys are really just
interested in like our updates and all
of that and but some people they they're
very extreme. I remember I posted a
video on my Snapchat and somebody was
like, "Oh, I know that you're going to
the US because AJ has given birth." And
it's coming from a good place, but you
have to wait. You have to wait for
people to make certain kind of
announcements before you like just come
out and make your statement. We all
sometimes have our thoughts. We all know
certain things, but it's okay for you to
wait for that person to put it out there
before you make it known that you know
because we've not said anything yet. But
yeah, so before this video will be up,
IG has to make her post about her birth
before anything. And that's what is
going to make this video a bit late. So
for all of you that cuz I know some of
you will come for me. This is why this
video will be late. I has to post first.
She has to make the announcement that
she has given birth. I can post my
travel vlog. But yeah, um they all went
out. They have like some places to go.
Me personally, I told them I didn't want
to go anywhere. I just wanted to stay at
home. I also want to just take out time
to clean a little. So when they come
back, at least you're coming back to a
clean space. So I want to do that. I'm
not showered yet. I'll shower then edit
video. And I think today will be the end
of this travel vlog. I'm not sure
because most times when I'm here, I just
leave my sister to do the vlogging. So
I'm not sure I'll do another vlog of my
stay in the US. But if something comes
up, something different so that it's not
like we're putting the same kind of
content. But if something comes up, I
might record. If not, this activity,
today's activity is going to be the end
of this travel vlog. So, let me get
started. By the way, my nighty, really
cute,
very cozy, is from Sunshine Collection
by Jesse. If you don't already know, my
sister has a clothing brand, Sunshine
Collection, that is Chinanu, and her
nightweares are super, super duper cute,
and they're tall girl friendly. Imagine
a tall girl like me. Look at the length
of this. It's so long. You don't have to
wearing like a jumper kind of pants. We
don't do that over here. So, make sure
you place your order. And this color is
so pretty. The material is also very
soft. You can wear it all day. You can
wear it to bed. I've literally worn this
all day. So, please shop from Sunshine
Collection by Jesse.
>> Alexa. Hey, Alexa. Play some afro beats.
[music]
Sales.
>> I'm an actor. I act. I'm used to facing
the camera, but when it comes to me
recording myself, I also vlog, but when
it comes to me recording myself and just
talking and talking, I'm more it's not
easy. I'm trying to get used to talking
to the camera like all this content
creator because there's money in content
creating and I want to make money. I
really want to make money because like
there's so much there's a lot I want to
do with money. I like to enjoy life.
Like that's one of my top top things.
And enjoying life means you have to
spend money. And the easiest way for me
to get money is by putting myself out
there. And these content creators in the
US and other countries, the money
they're making is high. It is well.
It is well with my country. Some people
are making money off Snapchat. Like
their Snapchat is monetized. My country
is limiting me. But we're still going to
make a lemonade out of lemon. This video
might not see the light of day. So, I'm
just going to keep yapping and yapping.
But if I watch it and I like it and I'm
saying something reasonable, then best
believe I'll post it. Cuz this year when
we're coming out of our shell, [music]
[music]
I love
seeing
[music]
>> [music]
>> I see
my [music]
[music]
Wow.